Guide to the Denise Levertov Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 5. Professional Papers
  - a. Correspondence
    - Bowling Green State University - Brandeis University (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Braude, Michael - Brookline Trust (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Brooklyn College - Bush Foundation (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Caedmon Records - California State University (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Calliopea Press (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Calyx - Capstone Editions (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Carle Place (NY) Public Schools - Catholic University (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Cedar Crest College - Central State University (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Centre International d'Etudes Poetiques - Centrum Foundation (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - C.G. Jung Center of New England - Cheetah (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Chelsea - Choice (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Christian Century - Church World Service (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Cistercian Studies Quarterly (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Citizens of the Imagination - Civil Liberties Union (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Clark, Jane - Cloud Chamber (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Coalition for a Nuclear Test Ban - College of Purchase (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - College of Saint Teresa - College of Wooster (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - College of Wooster - Colorado State University (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Columbia Magazine - Committee for Artistic and Intellectual Freedom in Iran (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Committee for Biafran Artists and Writers - Common Cause (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Commonweal - Composite Films (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Concord (MA) Free Public Library - Conjunctions (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Connecticut Poetry Circuit - Copper Canyon Press (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Copper Canyon Press Board of Directors Annual Meeting: minutes (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Cornell College - Council for Democracy in Korea (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Countryman Press (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Countryman Press [Pig Dreams]: contracts (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Coventure Ltd. - The Cresset Press (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Crisis in America - Curbstone (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Dance Perspectives - Decal (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Delta Epsilon Sigma Bulletin - Denver Public Library (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Denver Quarterly - The Dial Press (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Dictionary of Literary Biography [Anne Day Dewey text and correspondence] (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Dinah Shore College - Djerassi Foundation (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - DMZ - Doubleday (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Dover Publications - Dutton (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Earlham College - Eisenberg, Everett (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Elizabeth Press - Emmanuel Church, Boston (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Emory University - Equal-Time (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Ernst and Whinney - Ethos (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Evansville Review - Executive Office of the President (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Exile - Feinberg, Charles (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Fellowship - Feminist Writer's Guild (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Ferrall, Victor E. 1 TLS, 1997 Apr (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Festival franco-anglais de poesie [1 of 2], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Festival franco-anglais de poesie [2 of 2], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Fiction International - Fine Arts Work Center in Provincetown (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Fine, Larry - Five Trees Press (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Flashbacks - Folio (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library - Ford Foundation (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Fordham University - Fortune News (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Foundations and retreats (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Fourth Universalist Society in the City of New York - Free South Africa Fund (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Fresh Air with Terry Gross (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Fresh Fruit - Fuze (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Gale Research Co. - Genesis West (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - George Braziller, Inc. - Give Peace Project (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Glasgow Lectures, Washington and Lee University (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Goddard College - Granite Press (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Grassroots International - Great Hudson River Revival (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Great Neck (NY) Library - Grinnell College (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Grolier Club - Guatemala (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Guggenheim Foundation - Gustavus Adolphus College (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Hackett, Philip - Hampton Day School (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Hanging Loose (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Harbor Group - Harold Ober Associates (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Harper and Row (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Harper's Bazaar - Harvard Advocate (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Harvard College - Hawaii Literary Arts Council (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Healers' Resource Center - Hendrix College (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Henry Art Gallery, University of Washington - Heritage Printers, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Hika - Hobart and William Smith Colleges (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Hofstra University - Horse and Bird Press (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Hortulus - Howard Payne University (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - How(ever) - Hyder, Darrell (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - ICG - Imagine (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Immaculate Heart College - Indiana University (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Indiana University - Infact (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - In'hui - International Communication Agency (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - International Poetry Festival - International Society for Krishna Consciousness (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - International Summer Institutes - Inter-University Committee (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Intrepid - Islands and Continents (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Jackdaws - Janus Press (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - J.B. Lippincott Co. - John Barton Wolgamot Society (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation - John O'Hara Journal (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Jonathan Cape Ltd. - Justice in Our Schools (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Joubert Moon Poems: Zoland Books, Inc.: translations, reviews, contracts, ca. 1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Kalamazoo College - Kenyon College (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Killaly Press - Knox College (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - KPFA-FM - Kutztown State College (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Labor Alliance for Safe Energy - Lake Erie College (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Lake Forest College - Lemming (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - LeMorne College - Leverett House, Harvard (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Levertov Archive, correspondence w/ Paul Lacey, trustee [includes facsim: TLS 1937 Apr 23, London to Paul Levertoff, London / T.S. Eliot -- 1 p.; TLS, 1968 Nov 27, Newtown, CT to Denise Levertov / Louis Untermeyer -- 1 p.; ALS, n.d., The Old Fork to Denise Levertoff / W.J. de la Mare -- 2 pp.; ALS, 1967 Apr 16, Stonegrave York to Denise / fragment, unsigned] (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Lewis and Clark College - Liberation News Service (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Library Holding of Denise Levertov Materials (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Library Holding of Denise Levertov Materials: Beinecke Rare Books and Manuscripts Library, Yale University (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Library Holding of Denise Levertov Materials: Cornell University (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Library Holding of Denise Levertov Materials: Fales Library, New York University [correspondence with Cid Corman] (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Library Holding of Denise Levertov Materials: Houghton Library, Harvard University (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Library Holding of Denise Levertov Materials: Olin Library, Washington University [correspondence to Charles Gardiner] (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Library Journal - Library of Congress (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Life Magazine - Literary Review (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - "Literature and Medicine" Dialogue Group, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Literature and Medicine" Dialogue Group, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Literature and Medicine" Dialogue Group, 1978-1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Little, Brown and Co. - Longview Foundation, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Lordly and Dame, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Lordly and Dame, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Lordly and Dame, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles Police Department - Louisiana State University Press (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Loujon Press - Lynchburg College (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Macalester College - Macmillan Publishing Co. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Mademoiselle - The Malahat Review (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Mandala Community Workshop - Margaret Randall Legal Defense Committee (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Margins - Marshall University (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Marshroots - Massachusetts Acupuncture Association (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Massachusetts College of Art - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Massachusetts Review - Memphis State University (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Mercy College - Michigan State University (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Middlebury College - Mill Mountain Review (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Monica McCall, Inc. - Motchan's Design House (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Mother Jones: incoming correspondence (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Mother Jones: outgoing correspondence (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Milton Academy - Mithrander (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Mobilization for Survival - Modern Poetry Association (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Mounty Holyoke College - Muhlenberg College (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Mundelin College - The Mystics Quarterly (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Nantucket Review - Narwhal Press (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Nashua (NH) Public Library - Nassau County (NY) (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - The Nation, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - The Nation, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The Nation, 1967-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - The Nation [includes corespondence from Russell Edson, Richard Wilbur, Richard Eberhart] (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Nation: notes (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The Nation: Denise Levertov, editor (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The Nation: Denise Levertov, editor (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The Nation: Denise Levertov, editor (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Nation -- Vol. 188, no. 17, 1959 Apr 25 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression - National Chile Center (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - National Council of Teachers of English - National Educational Television (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - National Federation of State Poetry Societies - National Poetry Secretariat (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - National Public Radio - National Review [Hugh Kenner] (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - National Strike Information Center - National Writers' Union (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Nazareth College of Rochester - Nethers Community School (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - New Age - New Departures (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - New Dimensions: Denise Levertov, poetry editor (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - New Directions (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - New Directions, 1952-1959 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - New Directions, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - New Directions, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - New Directions, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - New Directions, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - New Directions, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - New Directions, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - New Directions, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - New Directions, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - New Directions, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - New Directions, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - New Directions, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - New Directions, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - New Directions, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - New Directions, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - New Directions, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - New Directions, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - New Directions, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - New Directions, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - New Directions, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - New Directions, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - New Directions, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - New Directions, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - New Directions, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - New Directions, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - New Directions, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - New Directions, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - New Directions: The Hive, etc. [business correspondence, royalty statements, publicity lists] (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - New England Campaign to Stop the Euromissiles - New England Review/Bread Loaf Quarterly (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - New England Telephone - New Letters (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - New Magazine Project - New Work (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - New York Center for Visual History - New Yorker (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - New York Poets for Peace - New York University (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - New York Review of Books - Nomad (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Non-Violence Project - Northwest Women's Studies Association (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Northwest Writers: contract (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Northwestern University - Nulle Part (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Oakland Tribune - Ohio University (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Ohio Wesleyan University - 100 Flowers Bookstore (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Ontario Review - Outsider (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Oxfam America - Oyez (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Pace College - Paideuma (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Paintbrush - Parkinson, Tom (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Parnassus - Partisan Defense Committee (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Partisan Review (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Pasadena City College - Pearl (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - P.E.N. American Center (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Pen and Palette Press - Pequod (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Permissions Requests (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Persea Books - Pine Manor Junior College (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Plaintiff - Poesis (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Poet - Poetry Australia (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Poetry Center of the Museum of Contemporary Art - Poetry Center, San Francisco State University (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Poetry Center of the YM and YWHA [i.e. 92nd Street Y] (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Poetry Center of the YM and YWHA [i.e. 92nd Street Y] (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Poetry Center of the YM and YWHA [i.e. 92nd Street Y] (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Poetry Center of the YM and YWHA [i.e. 92nd Street Y] (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Poetry Comics - Poetry East (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Poetry Flash - Poetry Now (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Poetry Magazine (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Poetry Project - Poetry Wales (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Poets and Writers (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Poets' Commune Publications - Poets On (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Poindexter Gallery - Portland Poetry Festival (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Possum Press - Pressworks (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Princeton University Press [includes TMs: Applewhite, James. "River Writing: An Eno Journal"] (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Private Funding Associates - Psychodrama Institute of Boston (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Publication correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Publication correspondence [New Directions, Broken Moon], 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Publication correspondence, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Public Citizen - Public Media Foundation (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Publishers Central Bureau - Pym-Randall Press (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Quadrille - Quarterly Review of Literature (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Queens College - Quixote Center (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Rabinowitz, Boudin and Standard - Radcliffe College (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Radcliffe Institute for Independent Study (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Radical Teacher - Randolph-Macon College (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Random House - Rapport (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Readers International - Reporter (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Requests for Denise Levertov involvement pending at time of death, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Resist - Resource Center for Nonviolence (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Review of Contemporary Fiction - Richard Fulton, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Rider College - Robertson (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Rochester Institue of Technology - Rosemary Hall (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Roth Publishing Co. - Rotterdamse Kunststich Westersingel (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Round Table - Rowe (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Royalty Statements (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Rusoff and Co., Bookdealers - Ruth Stephan Poetry Center (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Sacred Fire - St. Lawrence College (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - St. Louis County Heritage and Arts Center - St. Mary's College (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Saint Michael's College - Salve Regina College (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Sanctuary Education Committee - San Francisco Review (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco State University - Scandinavian Review (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Scholastic Magazines - Seer (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Seminar - Sewall, Richard (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Sgwu Literary Society - Short Stop Youth Emergency Shelter (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - A Shout in the Street - Skylight Productions (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Slavic Festival of the Arts, University of Kansas - Sojourners Magazine (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Solaris - Somerville, MA (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Somerville (MA) United Neighborhoods - Southampton College (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - South Bay Sanctuary Covenant - Southern Methodist University (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Southern Oregon State College - Southwest Texas State University (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Sou'wester - Spring Publications (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Springfield College - Spring Mobilization to End the War in Viet Nam (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Squeezebox - Stanford University (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Stanford University, 1984-1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Stanford University, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Stanford University English Department - State University College at Brockport (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - State University College Courtland - State University of N.Y. at Buffalo (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - State University of New York Harper - Stinktree (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Stone Country - Struga (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Student Peace - Sweet Briar (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Sycamore Review (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Sydney University - Syracuse University Press (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Talus - Temper (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Temple University - Tendril (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Texan Woman - Texas Review (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - The - This Issue (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Thomas Jefferson College - Thomas Y. Crowell Company (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Thresholds - Timberline (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Tialsman - Trenton College (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Trickster - Turuer (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Twigs - Two-Thirds, A Journal of Underdevelopment Studies (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Ulster - Union College (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Union of Bulgarian Writers - Unitarian Universalist (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - United Campus Ministry - The Universalist Church (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The University of Adelaide - University of Arizona (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - University of Bristish Columbia - University of Buffalo (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, Davis, Irvine (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - University of California, Los Angeles - University of California Press (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - University of Chatanooga - Cincinatti (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - The University of Colorado - Connecticut (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - University of Delaware - Idaho (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - University of Illinois - Iowa (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - University of Kansas - Louisville (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - University of Maine - Maryland (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - University of Massachusetts (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - University of Michigan (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - University of Minnesota - Montana (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - University of Natal - University of North Carolina (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - University of North Dakota - University of Pittsburgh Press (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - University of Rhode Island - University of Toronto (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - University of Utah - University of Washington (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - University of Western Australia (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - University of Wisconsin (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - University of Wisconsin Press (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - University Review - Utah State University (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Valley Peace - Vassar Quarterly (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Ventura - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Voices in the Wilderness - Voprosy Literatury (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Wabash - Wappingers Central School (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - War Resisters League, 1967-1982 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Warren - Washington University (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Watershed (California State Chico) - Watershed Foundation (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Waterville - Weigl (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Webster, Ed [Jazz with O.T.], Oct 1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Wellesley College - Wess (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Wesleyan University (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Wesleyan University Press, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Wesleyan University Press, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Wesleyan University Press, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Wesleyan University Press, 1965-1970 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Wesleyan University Press, 1974-1986 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - West End - Western Reserve (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Western States Arts Foundation (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Westigan Review - WFMT (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - WGBH (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - WGBH (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Wheaton College - William Carlos Williams (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - William Patterson College - Win (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Windows, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Wind - Women at Work (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom - Women's Institute for Freedom of the Press (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Women's Party - Women's Writer Center (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Wood - Woosters (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Worcester - Workshop Institute (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Work in Progress, 1997 Dec (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Working Papers (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - World Policy Conference - WRUR (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Writer's Digest, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - W.W. Norton and Company, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - W.W. Norton and Company, Inc. (letters received, as editor), 1966 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - W.W. Norton and Company, Inc., 1967-1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - W.W. Norton and Company, Inc., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - W.W. Norton and Company, Inc., 1980-1988 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Yaddo - Yale (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Yellow Moon - YWCA (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Zalkind and Zalkind - Zephyr Press (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - b. Awards and Honors
    - Academe Mallarme, 1990 Dec. 17, includes TLS from Guillevic (Box MC, Folder 1)
    - Conference on Christianity and Literature Lifetime Achievement award, 1994 Dec. 29 (Box OS-3, Folder 2)
    - Certificate of recognition of Denise Levertov by Michael Dukakis, Governor of Massachusetts, 1985 May 3 (Box OS-2, Folder 3)
    - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters Induction (facsim), 1980 May 22 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Contest judge: correspondence (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Contest judge: correspondence (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Contest judge: correspondence (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Contest judge: comments as judge, National Endowment for the Arts, 1987 Mar (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Contest judge: Grolier Poetry Peace Prize, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - A - J (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - National Book Award: Translation [for Guillevic, Selected Poems], 1970 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Recommendations for American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters Awards, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Speech presenting Denise Levertov as a candidate for Honorary Degree of Doctoral of Fine Arts, U.M.A., 1989 May (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - L - Z (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - c. Teaching Materials
    - Beloit Poetry Course: Teaching materials and correspondence [1 of 3], 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 31)